var sectiondata = {"sectiontag":"PIO","sectionname":"Post Interview Observations","qcount":16,"questions":{"1":{"question":"are you currently\r\nparticipating in a research study other than the BC Healthy Connections\r\nProject?\r","id":"PIO1","qnum":"q1","acount":2,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q1","id":"PIO1","answer":"[1] Yes","context_questions":{"qcount":1,"questions":{"1":{"question":"Could you provide the study team's contact information?\r","id":"PIO1_4","qnum":"q1-a1-q1","acount":2,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q1-a1-q1","id":"PIO1_4","answer":"[1] Yes","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"Name:\r","id":"PIO1_5","qnum":"q1-a1-q1-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q1-a1-q1-a1-q1","id":"PIO1_5","answer":"____"}}},"2":{"question":"Phone Number:\r","id":"PIO1_6","qnum":"q1-a1-q1-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q1-a1-q1-a1-q2","id":"PIO1_6","answer":"____"}}},"3":{"question":"Email Address:\r","id":"PIO1_7","qnum":"q1-a1-q1-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q1-a1-q1-a1-q3","id":"PIO1_7","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q1-a1-q1","id":"PIO1_4","answer":"[2] No"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q1","id":"PIO1","answer":"[2] No"}}},"2":{"question":"Now I'd like you to tell me about an aspect of parenting that you are\r\nlooking forward to?\r","id":"PIO2a","qnum":"q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2","id":"PIO2a","answer":"[____]"}}},"3":{"question":"These are all the questions I have for you today. Is there anything else\r\nyou think we should know about your pregnancy?\r","id":"PIO3","qnum":"q3","acount":2,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3","id":"PIO3","answer":"[1] Yes","context_questions":{"qcount":1,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What would you like to tell us?\r","id":"PIO3_1","qnum":"q3-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a1-q1","id":"PIO3_1","answer":"[____]"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q3","id":"PIO3","answer":"[2] No"}}},"4":{"question":"Date and time interview ended:\r","id":"PIO4","qnum":"q4","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4","id":"PIO4","answer":"timestamp"}}},"5":{"question":"Next are Post-Interview Observations to be answered confidentially by the\r\nScientific Field Interviewer immediately upon following the interview.\r","id":"PIO","qnum":"q5"},"6":{"question":"Did the participant inform you of their group assignment?\r","id":"PIO5","qnum":"q6","acount":2,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6","id":"PIO5","answer":"[1] Yes"},"2":{"qnum":"q6","id":"PIO5","answer":"[2] No"}}},"7":{"question":"Was the respondent cooperative?\r","id":"PIO6","qnum":"q7","acount":2,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7","id":"PIO6","answer":"[1] Yes"},"2":{"qnum":"q7","id":"PIO6","answer":"[2] No"}}},"8":{"question":"Did the respondent seem to have difficulty understanding the interview?\r","id":"PIO7","qnum":"q8","acount":2,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8","id":"PIO7","answer":"[1] Yes","context_questions":{"qcount":1,"questions":{"1":{"question":"If yes, explain (e.g. English as a second language, cognitive ability,\r\netc.) and INFORM THE SCIENTIFIC DIRECTOR:\r","id":"PIO7_1","qnum":"q8-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a1-q1","id":"PIO7_1","answer":"[____]"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q8","id":"PIO7","answer":"[2] No"}}},"9":{"question":"Did you have to reword any items for better understanding by the\r\nrespondent?\r","id":"PIO8","qnum":"q9","acount":2,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9","id":"PIO8","answer":"[1] Yes","context_questions":{"qcount":1,"questions":{"1":{"question":"If yes, identify items:\r","id":"PIO8_1","qnum":"q9-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a1-q1","id":"PIO8_1","answer":"[____]"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q9","id":"PIO8","answer":"[2] No"}}},"10":{"question":"Did the respondent become impatient or emotional in response to any items\r\nin the interview?\r","id":"PIO9","qnum":"q10","acount":2,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10","id":"PIO9","answer":"[1] Yes","context_questions":{"qcount":1,"questions":{"1":{"question":"If yes, identify items:\r","id":"PIO9_1","qnum":"q10-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a1-q1","id":"PIO9_1","answer":"[____]"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q10","id":"PIO9","answer":"[2] No"}}},"11":{"question":"Did the respondent have difficulty concentrating?\r","id":"PIO10a","qnum":"q11","acount":2,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q11","id":"PIO10a","answer":"[1] Yes"},"2":{"qnum":"q11","id":"PIO10a","answer":"[2] No"}}},"12":{"question":"In general, was the respondent unsure of answers?\r","id":"PIO10","qnum":"q12","acount":2,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q12","id":"PIO10","answer":"[1] Yes"},"2":{"qnum":"q12","id":"PIO10","answer":"[2] No"}}},"13":{"question":"Were there many interruptions? \r","id":"PIO11","qnum":"q13","acount":2,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q13","id":"PIO11","answer":"[1] Yes"},"2":{"qnum":"q13","id":"PIO11","answer":"[2] No"}}},"14":{"question":"Was privacy maintained throughout the interview?\r","id":"PIO12","qnum":"q14","acount":2,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q14","id":"PIO12","answer":"[1] Yes"},"2":{"qnum":"q14","id":"PIO12","answer":"[2] No","context_questions":{"qcount":1,"questions":{"1":{"question":"Explain:\r","id":"PIO12_1","qnum":"q14-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q14-a2-q1","id":"PIO12_1","answer":"[____]"}}}}}}}},"15":{"question":"Did you alter the interview procedures in any way?\r","id":"PIO13","qnum":"q15","acount":2,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q15","id":"PIO13","answer":"[1] Yes","context_questions":{"qcount":1,"questions":{"1":{"question":"Explain:\r","id":"PIO13_1","qnum":"q15-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q15-a1-q1","id":"PIO13_1","answer":"[____]"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q15","id":"PIO13","answer":"[2] No"}}},"16":{"question":"Any other comments you have on the interview?\r","id":"PIO14","qnum":"q16","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q16","id":"PIO14","answer":"[____]"}}}}}
